(competition in life)
(인생에서의 경쟁)
(The characters, events, groups, organizations and backgrounds of this drama are purely fictitious. We hereby inform you that)
(본 드라마에 등장하는 인물, 사건, 단체, 조직, 배경 등은 순전히 허구입니다. 이를 알려드립니다.)
(Episode 11)
(제11화)
Let's get started
시작하자
About PR Team 2 Agent Yoo Jae-min
홍보2팀 유재민 요원 소개
Acted by Park Yun-soo of PR Team 3
홍보3팀 박윤수 님이 맡았습니다.
The Personnel Committee will now be held
이제 인사위원회가 개최됩니다
before that
그것 앞에
There are other people who are going to be there in person
직접 가보실 분들도 계시고
who is it?
누구야?
Why is Director Goo here?
구국장님이 왜 여기 계시나요?
Director Goo, would you please preside over it?
구 감독님, 사회를 맡아주시겠어요?
How is this going?
어떻게 되어가나요?
(One week before the Personnel Committee is held)
(인사위원회 개최 일주일 전)
(Se Yong)
(세용)
Please come in
오세요
(General Manager of Sales Department)
(영업부장)
Please cancel the convening of the personnel committee
인사위원회 소집을 취소해주세요
Then I'm afraid I can't do it
그러면 난 할 수 없을 것 같아
Do you really have no idea what the real problem is?
진짜 문제가 무엇인지 정말 모르시나요 ?
The PR office should not be blamed for this matter!
이 문제에 대해 홍보실을 비난해서는 안됩니다!
No, the PR office must take full responsibility for this
아니요, 이에 대한 모든 책임은 홍보실에서 져야 합니다.
And not just them, but you too
그리고 그들뿐만 아니라 당신도 마찬가지입니다
The company is not a charity
회사는 자선단체가 아니다
How long will I tolerate you?
나는 언제까지 당신을 참을 것인가?
Why should we suffer the consequences of your incompetence?
왜 우리가 당신의 무능함으로 인해 고통을 받아야 합니까?
Not to mention not just once, but twice!
한 번도 아니고 두 번이나 말할 것도 없습니다!
If nothing can be done to remedy this situation, Shi Yonghui will collapse.
이 상황을 해결하기 위해 아무것도 할 수 없다면 Shi Yonghui는 무너질 것입니다.
I want to prevent that from happening
그런 일이 일어나지 않도록 하고 싶어요
And that's it for you!
그리고 그게 바로 당신을 위한 것입니다!
Is the personnel committee going to be convened so soon?
인사위원회가 그렇게 빨리 소집되나요?
And the target is not the sales manager but an employee of the public relations office?
그리고 그 대상은 영업관리자가 아니라 홍보실 직원인가요?
Doesn’t that mean the company wants to push us to take bullets?
그건 회사가 우리에게 총알을 쏘도록 강요하고 싶어한다는 뜻이 아닙니까 ?
Seeing them do all the dirty things makes people more convinced that there must be something evil.
그들이 온갖 더러운 일을 하는 것을 보면 사람들은 뭔가 악한 일이 있음에 틀림없다는 확신을 갖게 됩니다.
What on earth were they trying to cover up to get to this point?
도대체 그들은 이 지경까지 오기 위해 무엇을 은폐하려고 했던 걸까요 ?
Hello
안녕하세요
When did Team Leader Song get involved and how did he get involved?
송팀장은 언제 , 어떻게 참여하게 되었나요?
I asked him
그에게 물어 보았다
- But he avoided the question - would he openly admit it?
-하지만 그는 질문을 피했습니다 . 공개적으로 인정할까요?
How could any fool go and ask him face to face?
어리석은 자가 어떻게 가서 그분께 대면하여 물을 수 있겠습니까?
And you are the fool
그리고 당신은 바보입니다
Damn it, you scared me
젠장, 너 때문에 겁이 났어
You said you want to hold an emergency countermeasures meeting?
긴급대책회의를 열고 싶다고 했죠?
No matter what the name of this meeting is,
이 모임의 이름은 무엇이든 상관없습니다.
But the current situation is indeed urgent
그런데 지금 상황은 참으로 긴급하다.
What will happen if a personnel committee is convened?
인사위원회가 소집되면 어떻게 되나요?
That's just a necessary process for making punishments
그건 처벌을 위해서 꼭 필요한 과정일 뿐이에요
Now there are rumors outside
지금 밖에는 소문이 떠돌고 있어
If you are punished, it will be Director Goo’s turn next.
벌칙을 받으면 다음은 구 감독 차례다.
Why is everyone targeting Director Goo?
왜 다들 구감독을 노리는 걸까요?
Why is everyone so anxious to remove her?
왜 모두가 그녀를 제거하고 싶어하는 걸까요?
Now that's not the point
이제 그게 요점이 아니야
But what do you two plan to do?
그런데 너희 둘은 무엇을 할 계획인가?
This forged ingredient analysis list given to Houji by Team Leader Song
송팀장이 후지에게 준 위조된 성분분석표
I think we should start investigating from here
내 생각엔 여기서부터 조사를 시작해야 할 것 같아
Scared me
날 무섭게했다
It's clearly visible from outside
밖에서도 확연히 눈에 띕니다
Why should countermeasures meetings be held in the company?
왜 사내 대책회의를 개최해야 합니까?
-There are eyeliners everywhere here -Seunghee
- 여기저기 아이라이너가 있어요 - 승희
What you plan to do is also our share.
당신이 하려는 일도 우리 몫이다.
Seung Hee
승희
It seems like I haven’t seen Agent Xu for a long time.
Xu 요원을 오랫동안 보지 못한 것 같습니다.
I also want to help you
나도 당신을 돕고 싶어요
I can't put all the blame on you two.
나는 너희 둘에게 모든 책임을 돌릴 수 없다.
That's wrong
그건 틀렸어요
Agent Xu
쉬 요원
I can't tell you are so good at talking
네가 말을 그렇게 잘한다고는 말할 수 없어
What to do? What to start with?
무엇을 해야 할까요? 무엇부터 시작할까요?
My problem is no longer within our capabilities
내 문제는 더 이상 우리의 능력 범위 내에 있지 않습니다.
Let’s all help solve Agent Liu’s problem together .
모두 함께 Liu 요원의 문제를 해결하도록 도와주세요.
Now who leaked that report?
그럼 그 보고서는 누가 유출한 걸까요?
It's no longer the point
더 이상 그게 중요한 게 아니야
Then go inquire about the sales team.
그런 다음 영업팀에 대해 문의해 보세요.
My connections are no joke
내 인맥이 장난이 아니네
but
하지만
We should also solve the problem of Agent Park, right?
박요원 문제 도 해결해야겠죠 ?
That negative marketing
그 네거티브 마케팅
I heard from Jihyo that you were actually firmly opposed to it at the beginning.
사실 처음에는 확고한 반대를 했다고 지효한테 들었어요 .
So why should you be punished alone?
그렇다면 왜 혼자 처벌을 받아야합니까?
I believe you and like you
나는 당신을 믿고 당신을 좋아합니다
Hey, what is this?
야, 이게 뭐야?
By the way, this is the ingredient analysis table, show it to them.
그런데 이게 성분분석표인데 보여주세요.
Well, that is to say
뭐, 그러니까 말이야
This is the ingredient analysis list given to Houji by Team Leader Song
송팀장이 후지에게 준 성분분석표입니다.
right
오른쪽
This is the analysis table I commissioned separately.
제가 별도로 의뢰한 분석표입니다.
(Is Shi Yong not related to the death of the boss of a certain outsourcing company ?)
(시용은 특정 외주업체 사장의 죽음과 관련이 없는 걸까요?)
Well, this is very well written.
뭐, 이거 아주 잘 쓰여졌네요.
But Jae Min…
그런데 재민이...
Huiying
후이잉
This is not something you should feel guilty about
이건 네가 죄책감을 느껴야 할 일이 아니야
You didn't peek on purpose, you just happened to see it
일부러 엿본 게 아니고 우연히 봤을 뿐인데
Didn’t you also tell Cai Min?
채민에게도 말하지 않았나요?
I only said it after I decided to write the report. At most, it was just to inform him.
보고서를 작성하기로 결정한 후에야 그 말을 했을 뿐 , 기껏해야 그에게 알리기 위한 말뿐이었습니다.
If you pretended not to know for Jaemin's sake, would you feel better now?
재민이를 위해서 모른 척 했다면 이제 좀 나아질까요?
I don't think so, you must be very anxious
아닌 것 같은데 많이 불안하시겠어요
I guess we don't have to worry about Jae Min
재민 걱정은 안 해도 될 것 같아요
I like you
좋아해요
I said I like you
난 당신을 좋아한다고 말했어요
Come date with me
나랑 데이트하자
You don’t have a date right now, do you?
지금은 데이트 상대가 없지, 그렇지?
Have you ever dated a girl?
여자랑 사귄 적 있어?
Here we go again, you asked the same question
다시 시작합니다. 같은 질문을 하셨습니다.
But does it matter whether you’ve been in a relationship or not?
하지만 연애를 했는지 안 했는지가 중요한가요?
important
중요한
Very important
매우 중요
in Korea
한국에서는
This kind of relationship cannot be disclosed easily
이런 관계는 쉽게 공개할 수 없어
Suppose someone asks you if you have a date
누군가 당신에게 데이트 상대가 있냐고 묻는다면
Then he asked when you plan to get married.
그러더니 언제 결혼할 생각이냐고 물었다.
You can't answer this kind of question at all
이런 질문에는 전혀 대답할 수 없습니다
Over time, you will start to think about giving up.
시간이 지남에 따라 포기에 대해 생각하기 시작할 것입니다.
“I want to show off my significant other to others and receive blessings from others
“다른 사람에게 나의 애인을 자랑하고 싶고 , 다른 사람으로부터 축복을 받고 싶어요.
I also want to have ordinary love in the eyes of others.”
나도 다른 사람들의 눈에 평범한 사랑을 갖고 싶다”고 말했다.
In the end you will choose to leave
결국 당신은 떠나는 것을 선택하게 될 것이다.
Those who think there is no difference
별차이 없다고 생각하시는 분들은
Maybe I haven't thought about this problem at all
어쩌면 나는 이 문제에 대해 전혀 생각하지 않았을 수도 있다
In short
요컨대
It's something to be grateful for when someone likes me, so thank you.
누군가가 나를 좋아해 준다는 건 고마운 일이니까, 고마워요.
It seems…
그것은 보인다…
You are quite extreme
너 좀 극단적이구나
As you say
당신이 말한대로
In Korea, as long as you get blessings from others, you can have an ordinary love in the eyes of others.
한국에서는 다른 사람의 축복을 받으면 다른 사람의 눈에도 평범한 사랑을 가질 수 있습니다.
Will they never break up?
그들은 결코 헤어지지 않을 것인가?
If we break up because of other people
다른 사람 때문에 헤어지면
That love was doomed to fail from the beginning
그 사랑은 처음부터 실패할 운명이었어
If not, it means that the breakup was just because we no longer loved each other.
그렇지 않다면, 그것은 우리가 더 이상 서로를 사랑하지 않기 때문에 이별했다는 뜻입니다.
I've already confessed to you
난 이미 당신에게 고백했어요
But my desire to date you has not changed. Please think about it carefully.
하지만 당신과 사귀고 싶은 마음은 변함이 없으니 잘 생각해보시기 바랍니다.
I think the problem is not with me, but with you
문제는 나한테 있는 게 아니라 너한테 있는 것 같아
Look at the way you are pretending to be awesome
멋진 척하는 모습 좀 보세요
I am already very powerful, don’t you know?
나는 이미 매우 강력합니다. 모르시나요?
That really makes you want to curse, right?
정말 욕하고 싶게 만드는군요, 그렇죠?
Damn it makes me want to curse
젠장 욕하고 싶게 만드네요
Calm down, don't get excited
진정해, 흥분하지 마
He said I was incompetent
그 사람은 내가 무능력하다고 했어
I really don’t understand which period drama Se Yong is acting in
세용이가 어떤 시대극에 출연하는지 정말 모르겠어요
Alas, Seyong is essentially a pharmaceutical company.
아아, 세용이는 본질적으로 제약회사입니다.
that kind of place
그런 곳
somewhat conservative
다소 보수적
They don't even have any common sense
그사람들 상식도 없네
Because the standards are different
기준이 다르기 때문에
Hey, how can there be any so-called standards for common sense?
아니, 소위 상식의 기준이라는 것이 어떻게 있을 수 있겠습니까?
What the public thinks is right is common sense
대중이 옳다고 생각하는 것은 상식이다
If everyone has their own standards, how can it be called common sense?
사람마다 자신만의 기준이 있다면, 그것을 어떻게 상식이라고 할 수 있겠습니까?
Have worked in the company for a long time
오랫동안 회사에서 일해왔어
People's standards may be shaken
사람들의 기준이 흔들릴 수도 있다
Otherwise, why would anyone be willing to accept the mistakes made by company representatives?
그렇지 않다면 왜 회사 대표가 저지른 실수를 기꺼이 받아들이겠습니까 ?
Are you still sacrificing your life for the company?
아직도 회사를 위해 목숨을 바치고 계십니까?
Not at all
별말씀을요
That's because they are afraid
그 이유는 그들이 두려워하기 때문이다
The life I have devoted my whole life to is worthless.
내가 평생을 바친 삶은 가치가 없습니다.
Only then will your own value change...
그래야만 자신의 가치관이 바뀔 것이다...
I really don’t understand that kind of person, my God!
저는 그런 사람을 정말 이해할 수가 없어요, 맙소사!
I heard what you said
나는 당신이 말한 것을 들었습니다
Suddenly reminds me of a certain bastard from before
갑자기 예전에 어떤 놈이 생각나네
Which bastard?
어느 놈?
When I was an agent
내가 대리인이었을 때
Reported a supervisor’s wrongdoing to the Inspection Team
감독관의 비위행위를 감사팀에 신고
But some bastard who knows that better than anyone else
근데 그걸 누구보다 잘 아는 새끼가
But when questioned by the inspection team, he denied it completely
하지만 조사단의 질문에는 전면 부인했다.
Choose to protect your boss
상사를 보호하기로 선택하세요
This is too ridiculous
이건 너무 말도 안돼
So I was labeled an insider whistleblower.
그래서 내부고발자로 낙인찍혔어요.
After that, everyone obviously avoided me
그 뒤로는 다들 날 피하는 게 당연해
I was not admitted through open recruitment in the first place.
애초에 공개채용으로 합격한 건 아니었어요.
But he was a journalist and was specially hired.
그러나 그는 언론인이었고 특별히 고용되었습니다.
Now I'm even more annoying
지금은 더 짜증나네
Even promotion has become out of reach
홍보조차 불가능해졌어
so i left
그래서 난 떠났어
I'm talking about Se Rong
세롱에 대해서 말하는 거야
Shi Rong?
시 롱?
Yes, Se Yong
응, 세용아
Oh my God! So fed up
맙소사! 너무 지쳤어
drink
마시다
But Yi Jung
그런데 이정이
Don't give up
포기하지 마세요
Why?
왜?
Although you may not be able to change anything on your own
스스로 아무것도 바꿀 수 없을지라도
But if you don't care about me
하지만 당신이 나에게 관심이 없다면
There's no chance to change again
다시 바꿀 기회는 없어
(Representative, Xu Dongxun)
(대표 서동순)
-Do you want to go there now? -Yes, senior
-지금 거기로 갈래? -네, 선배
I heard that you prepared those all by yourself.
그걸 다 직접 준비했다고 들었어요.
You should let others share the burden.
다른 사람들이 부담을 공유하도록 해야 합니다.
Because it concerns Se-yong
세용이 걱정이니까
Everyone is running for Ang's bakery
모두가 앙의 빵집을 향해 달려가고 있어요
I should do this
나는 이것을 해야 한다
After all, Shirong is also our client.
결국 Shirong도 우리의 고객입니다.
we have no choice
우리에겐 선택의 여지가 없어
But you can’t ask them for money, right?
하지만 돈을 요구할 수는 없잖아요?
right
오른쪽
They should hope that we can give away online monitoring services
그들은 우리가 온라인 모니터링 서비스를 제공할 수 있기 를 바랍니다.
I think so
그렇게 생각해요
Anyway, thank you for your hard work
어쨌든, 노고에 감사드립니다
- No - That’s right
- 아니 - 그렇죠
It's a representative's job to deal with this kind of thing, right?
이런 일을 처리하는 게 대표의 몫이겠죠?
That's right
좋아요
oh
오
good
좋은
I heard that Representative Xu worked very hard on this matter.
쉬 대표가 이 문제에 대해 매우 열심히 노력했다고 들었습니다.
so what?
그래서 뭐?
He came here for online monitoring of protein powder.
그는 단백질 파우더의 온라인 모니터링을 위해 이곳에 왔습니다.
It is required by the directors
이사가 요구하는 사항입니다.
that?
저것?
In short, the responsible unit is Global Communications, I believe you will do a good job.
한마디로 담당 부서는 글로벌커뮤니케이션즈인데, 잘 하실 거라 믿습니다.
No, you must behave well
아니, 잘 지내야 해
Shirong is not a company that is easy to bully
시롱은 쉽게 괴롭히는 회사가 아닙니다
How easy is it to make other people's money?
다른 사람의 돈을 버는 것이 얼마나 쉬운가요?
Isn't it?
그렇지 않나요?
Yes, you are right
그래 네가 맞아
At least Director Chen still wants to talk to you in person.
적어도 첸 이사님은 아직도 직접 만나 얘기하고 싶어하시네요.
Yes, thank you for taking such good care of me
네, 이렇게 잘 챙겨주셔서 감사해요
The situation is not optimistic, right?
상황은 낙관적이지 않죠?
right
오른쪽
In addition to Representative Lin’s personal account
린 대표의 개인 계정 외에
And all social media comment areas managed by Shi Yong
그리고 모든 SNS 댓글 영역은 시용님이 관리하고 있습니다
It's best to close them all temporarily
일시적으로 모두 닫는 것이 가장 좋습니다.
I checked on the way here
여기까지 오는 길에 확인했어요
The Internet is now filled with calls for crusade
이제 인터넷은 십자군 전쟁을 촉구하는 글로 가득 차 있습니다.
OK
좋아요
Yes, thank you for confirming it for us
네, 확인해 주셔서 감사합니다
Okay, I'll take my leave then
알았어, 그럼 난 이만 갈게
Wait, that...
잠깐, 그거...
I heard your clients are also involved.
귀사의 고객도 참여하고 있다고 들었습니다.
I didn't expect you to take care of this personally.
나는 당신이 이것을 개인적으로 처리할 것이라고 기대하지 않았습니다.
On the one hand, I also think our request is too unreasonable.
한편으로는 우리의 요구가 너무 무리한 것이라고도 생각합니다.
as i just said
내가 방금 말했듯이
Global Communications is a partner of Serong
글로벌커뮤니케이션즈는 세롱의 파트너입니다
All we do is try our best to meet customer requirements
우리가 하는 일은 고객 요구 사항을 충족하기 위해 최선을 다하는 것입니다.
Please remember this
이것을 기억해주세요
Okay, I'll keep it in mind
알았어, 명심할게
OK, bye
알았어 잘가
take care
잘 지내세요
He also gave me the ingredients test report from the Food and Drug Administration.
식품의약품안전처에서 발행한 성분시험성적서도 주셨어요.
You have nothing to do with this?
당신은 이 일과 아무 관련이 없나요?
What did you say?
뭐라고 하셨나요?
If you didn't hear it, let me ask again
못 들었으면 다시 물어볼게
Team leader
팀 리더
You and this protein powder incident
너와 이번 단백질가루 사건
No connection at all?
전혀 연결이 되지 않나요?
Agent Guo, if you know anything, just tell me.
궈 요원님, 아시는 게 있으면 말씀해 주세요.
Senior, I really don’t know anything.
선배님, 저는 정말 아무것도 모릅니다.
How could you, the ace of the sales team, know nothing?
영업팀의 에이스인 당신이 어떻게 아무것도 모르겠습니까 ?
-Senior -huh?
- 선배 - 응?
I really don't know anything
난 정말 아무것도 몰라
That was all done by Team Leader Zhao alone.
그것은 모두 자오 팀장 혼자 한 일이었습니다.
I go first
내가 먼저 가
Agent Guo
구오 요원
Team Leader Zhao has the sole authority to handle the upgrade of the protein powder formula this time.
자오 팀장은 이번에 단백질 파우더 포뮬러의 업그레이드
So the other groups don’t know anything about it.
그래서 다른 그룹은 그것에 대해 아무것도 모릅니다.
This is the ingredient analysis information you requested
고객님께서 요청하신 성분분석 정보입니다
Only this?
만이?
right
오른쪽
research group to date
현재까지의 연구 그룹
I still have the ingredient analysis table previously issued by Dongxin.
예전에 동신에서 발행한 성분분석표가 아직도 남아있습니다.
(Equipment warehouse)
(비품 창고)
Yes, there are limits to what we can do
예, 우리가 할 수 있는 일에는 한계가 있습니다
Do you want
당신은 원하십니까
Report directly to the inspection team?
검사팀에 직접 보고하시겠습니까?
Do you want everyone to quit?
다들 그만두고 싶나요?
Then the public relations office will really collapse.
그러면 홍보실이 정말 무너질 것 같아요.
Houji should be able to survive.
Houji는 살아남을 수 있어야합니다.
That brat said he didn't want to have anything to do with it
그 새끼는 그 일과 아무 상관도 하고 싶지 않다고 했어
I will survive too
나도 살아남을 거야
Otherwise, who will make the money for milk powder?
그렇지 않으면 누가 분유로 돈을 벌겠습니까?
So don’t even think about reporting it to the inspection team.
그러니까 감찰팀에 신고할 생각은 하지 마세요.
In this case
이 경우
I'll tell you what's really the key
진짜 핵심이 뭔지 알려줄게
Team Leader Song
송팀장
We need to investigate him further.
그를 더 조사해야 합니다.
Then do you want to meet the other team leaders?
그럼 다른 팀장들도 만나보실래요?
I'll go find Team Leader Chi
치 팀장을 찾으러 갈게요
Team leader pool?
팀 리더 풀?
This is no longer a problem we can solve
이건 더 이상 우리가 해결할 수 있는 문제가 아니다
what i can do for you
내가 당신을 위해 무엇을 할 수 있습니까?
Just to help you reduce the punishment as much as possible
처벌을 최대한 줄일 수 있도록 도와드립니다.
But I'm not sure now whether I can do it
그런데 지금은 내가 할 수 있을지 확신이 안 섰다.
Not to mention the other team members' affairs.
다른 팀원들의 일은 말할 것도 없고요.
besides
게다가
Senior Song should also have his own reasons
송 선배도 나름의 이유가 있겠지
And I can't ignore that
그리고 난 그걸 무시할 수 없어
Caimin agent
카이민제
It seems wrong to do this
이렇게 하는 것은 잘못된 것 같습니다
How can I…
내가 어떻게 할 수있는…
How could I stab Team Leader Song in the back?
어떻게 송팀장의 등을 찌를 수 있겠습니까?
No, I'm not asking you to do this, Team Leader Cui
아니요, 이렇게 하라고 하는 게 아닙니다, 추이 팀장
i just hope you
난 그냥 당신이 바랍니다
Can you help us thoroughly investigate the ins and outs of this matter?
이 문제의 내용을 철저하게 조사하는 데 도움을 주실 수 있나요?
That's what it means to me
그게 나에게 의미하는 바야
You want to investigate deeply everything related to Team Leader Song?
송 팀장과 관련된 모든 것을 깊이 조사하고 싶습니까?
me
나
The reason why I can still stay in this company till now
내가 지금까지 이 회사에 머물 수 있는 이유
It depends on loyalty
충성도에 달려있습니다
I will never do anything that harms the organization or my colleagues
나는 조직이나 동료에게 피해를 주는 일은 절대 하지 않겠다.
Maybe you will be disappointed after hearing this
어쩌면 이 말을 듣고 실망할 수도 있습니다.
But that's who I am
하지만 그게 바로 나야
Just pretend that what we met today never happened.
오늘 우리가 만난 일은 결코 일어나지 않은 일이라고 가정해 보세요.
Take care of yourself
몸 조심하세요
I'll pay the bill
내가 지불할게
Let’s go find Director Goo
구 감독을 찾으러 가자
She has the right to investigate this matter and I believe she will do the same.
그녀는 이 문제를 조사할 권리가 있으며 나는 그녀도 그렇게 할 것이라고 믿습니다.
But there is so little evidence
하지만 증거가 너무 부족해서
The only evidence we have is the ingredient analysis table
우리가 가지고 있는 유일한 증거는 성분 분석표뿐입니다.
Besides, her current situation is not very good either.
게다가 현재 상황도 별로 좋지 않다.
I know everything
나는 모든 것을 알고 있다
But she's our last resort
하지만 그녀는 우리의 최후의 수단이야
It also takes courage to ask a good boss for help
좋은 상사에게 도움을 요청하는 데도 용기가 필요합니다
About the Victims of the Protein Powder Incident
단백질분말 사건 피해자에 대하여
What does the sales team think?
영업팀은 어떻게 생각하나요?
Yes, because this incident is not simple
네 이번 사건은 단순하지 않으니까
Therefore, the sales team also attaches great importance to this matter and decided to recall all products
따라서 영업팀에서도 이 문제를 매우 중요하게 생각하며 전 제품을 리콜하기로 결정했습니다.
good
좋은
In addition, reporter Choi Huiying of Daguo Ilbo
또 다궈일보 최희영 기자는
The ingredient analysis table she presented...
그녀가 제시한 성분분석표..
but
하지만
The analysis form provided to us by the Food and Drug Administration shows that there is no problem
식품의약품안전처에서 우리에게 제공한 분석서는 문제가 없는 것으로 나타났습니다.
certainly
틀림없이
Analysis results will vary depending on the sample analyzed.
분석 결과는 분석된 샘플에 따라 달라집니다.
I guess that's why the company decided to recall all the products
그래서 회사가 모든 제품을 리콜하기로 결정한 것 같아요.
So the samples are different?
그럼 샘플이 다른건가요?
right
오른쪽
That, Director Goo
그거, 구 감독님
According to Director Chen
첸 감독의 말에 따르면
The company has decided to take punishment
회사는 처벌을 결정했다
And punishing those two people is the biggest apology the company can express.
그리고 그 두 사람을 처벌하는 것이 회사가 표현할 수 있는 가장 큰 사과다.
Is Director Chen in the company now?
지금 첸 이사님이 회사에 계시나요?
He scheduled a vacation before the personnel committee convened.
그는 인사위원회가 열리기 전에 휴가를 계획했다.
The phone is also turned off
전화기도 꺼져있고
What's the point of having a meeting with just a few of us ?
우리 중 소수만이 회의를 갖는 것이 무슨 의미가 있습니까 ?
This matter seems to have been decided...
이 문제는 결정된 것 같습니다 ...
okay, I get it
알았어, 알겠어
You guys go out
너희들은 나가라
Director Goo seems to be helpless.
구 감독은 무기력해 보인다.
that's what i want to say
그게 내가 말하고 싶은 거야
This is what I just wanted to say
내가 딱 말하고 싶었던 건 바로 이거야
Wait, you really have to watch the PR office.
잠깐만요, 홍보실을 꼭 지켜봐야 해요.
Reduced to a state of fragmentation?
조각화 상태로 축소되었습니까?
What can we do? The PR office is the weakest department
우리는 무엇을 할 수 있나요? 홍보실은 가장 취약한 부서다.
Um
음
This is not something that a mere sales team leader can accomplish alone.
이는 단순한 영업팀장 혼자서 할 수 있는 일이 아닙니다.
Unless someone high-level is helping him behind the scenes
높은 레벨의 누군가가 뒤에서 그를 도와주지 않는 한
right
오른쪽
And that ingredient analysis table...
그리고 저 성분분석표...
Team Leader Song Xuantai just reported this matter to me
팀 리더 Song Xuantai가 방금 이 문제를 나에게 보고했습니다.
He said because the samples were different
샘플이 다르다고 하더군요
The ingredient analysis table provided by the Food and Drug Administration shows that Se Yong’s sample did not ask...
식품의약품안전처가 제공한 성분 분석표에 따르면 세용 씨의 시료는 묻지 않았다..
No
아니요
The samples are the same
샘플이 똑같네요
The person who provided the analysis table was also team leader Song Xuantai
분석표를 제공한 사람도 송쉬안타이 팀장이다.
You said the samples are the same?
샘플이 똑같다고 했죠?
right
오른쪽
Director Gu
구 이사
I didn't express my suspicions to save myself.
나는 자신을 구하기 위해 의심을 표현하지 않았습니다.
I don't think so either
나도 그렇게 생각하지 않아
What can be found out or resolved before convening the personnel committee ?
인사위원회를 소집하기 전에 알아내거나 해결할 수 있는 사항은 무엇입니까 ?
if not?
그렇지 않다면?
The reason why I decided to tell you these things
내가 이런 말을 하기로 결심한 이유
Because of
때문에
I don't think you're going to ignore this like the rest of Seyong's senior management.
나는 당신이 세용의 다른 고위 경영진처럼 이것을 무시할 것이라고 생각하지 않습니다.
You won't give up just because you're in a disadvantaged position.
자신이 불리한 입장에 있다고 해서 포기하지 않을 것입니다.
Even after the personnel committee ends
인사위원회가 끝난 뒤에도
I also hope you can find out about this
나는 또한 당신이 이것에 대해 알아낼 수 있기를 바랍니다
but after that
하지만 그 이후에는
I might not be alive anymore
난 더 이상 살아 있지 않을지도 몰라
In other words, if you want to launch an investigation
즉, 조사를 시작하려는 경우
We have to hurry up before the personnel committee convenes.
인사위원회가 열리기 전에 서둘러야 해요.
so
그래서
It 's time for us to stop being silent and show them.
이제 우리는 침묵을 멈추고 그들에게 보여줄 때입니다.
As the saying goes, "A dog in a hurry will jump over the wall."
“개는 서두르면 벽을 뛰어넘는다”는 말이 있다.
So what to do?
그래서 뭐 할까?
-Will everyone resign together? -Don't do that
-모두 함께 사퇴할 것인가? - 그러지 마세요
Slogans like "We want to get to the bottom of things"
"우리는 사물의 근본 원인을 파악하고 싶다" 와 같은 슬로건
How about uploading it to the company discussion forum?
회사 토론방에 올려보시면 어떨까요?
"Find out the truth thoroughly"?
"진실을 철저히 밝혀라"?
You are exaggerating too
너도 과장하는구나
Have you ever participated in a protest? Do you know what a petrol bomb is?
시위에 참여한 적이 있나요? 휘발유 폭탄이 무엇인지 아시나요?
It seems you are quite experienced
경험이 꽤 많으신 것 같네요
In fact, Agent Liu was also wrong, wasn't he?
사실 Liu 요원도 틀렸죠?
I heard that reporter is his friend
기자가 친구라고 들었는데
This means that he has no self-awareness as a publicist
홍보 담당자로서의 자각이 없다는 뜻이다.
Also, the person mentioned in the forum post is Agent Park.
또한, 포럼 게시물에 언급된 인물은 박요원입니다.
In my opinion, those who do wrong should be punished
내 생각에는 잘못한 사람은 처벌을 받아야 한다고 생각해요
wrong
잘못된
it's not like that
그건 그렇지 않아
Agent Yoo did not leak any information.
유 요원은 어떠한 정보도 유출하지 않았습니다.
Besides, that's not the point.
게다가 그게 요점이 아니거든요.
Something happened but you just want to cover it up, that's the real problem
무슨 일이 일어났는데 그냥 덮으려는 거, 그게 진짜 문제야
As for Agent Park
에이전트 파크의 경우
She's just a scapegoat
그녀는 단지 희생양일 뿐이야
You don’t even know this and you dare to call yourself a public relations office employee?
이런 것도 모르고 감히 홍보실 직원이라고 자칭하겠습니까?
Anyway, let’s wait until the disciplinary action comes out.
아무튼 징계 나올 때까지 기다려보자.
Maybe they'll get away with it.
어쩌면 그들은 그것으로 도망갈 것입니다.
Then we will look like fools
그러면 우리는 바보처럼 보일 것이다
Don't gather everyone to talk about what you have and what you don't have.
당신이 가지고 있는 것과 가지고 있지 않은 것에 대해 이야기하기 위해 모든 사람을 모으지 마십시오.
Where did Agent Park go?
박요원은 어디로 갔나요?
She just said she was going to the hospital
방금 병원에 간다고 하더군요
Visit the proud bakery owner
자랑스러운 빵집 주인을 만나보세요
I went to see him too
나도 그 사람을 만나러 갔어
Why are you going?
너는 왜가는거야?
Because I feel so sorry
너무 미안하니까
The thought of someone passing out from the amount of stress I'm under
내가 겪고 있는 스트레스로 인해 누군가 기절할 것이라는 생각
My mood is very heavy
기분이 많이 무거워요
The current market response is gradually changing
현재 시장의 반응은 점차 변화하고 있습니다.
Ang’s bakery sales have also gradually picked up
앙 베이커리 매출도 점차 회복세
Sorry, boss
죄송해요 사장님
it's all my fault
그것은 모두 내 잘못이야
You say you have no choice
당신은 선택의 여지가 없다고 말해요
no
아니요
That's what everyone says to me
다들 나한테 그렇게 말하는데
But I should fight to the death to stop them
하지만 난 그들을 막기 위해 목숨을 걸고 싸워야 해
If I can't do that, then I should leave that company.
그렇게 할 수 없다면 그 회사를 떠나야 합니다.
but
하지만
Sorry I didn't do that
미안 내가 그러지 않았어
I'm also sorry that I delayed coming until now.
저도 지금까지 늦어서 죄송합니다.
to be honest
솔직히 말하자면
I'm scared
나 무서워
I'm afraid that Boss Huang might have something unexpected happen to him
황 상사에게 예상치 못한 일이 일어날까 두렵습니다.
I'm also afraid that after we actually meet, you will all blame me.
그리고 우리가 실제로 만난 후에 여러분 모두가 저를 비난할 까봐 두렵습니다.
sorry
죄송합니다
that…
저것…
If I have to say it, it’s Se Rong’s fault.
굳이 말하자면 세롱이 잘못이다.
I still know this
난 아직도 이걸 알아
But look
하지만 보세요
You are the only one who apologizes
사과하는 사람은 너뿐이야
How long has it been since I uploaded that post? Saeyong hasn’t even made an official statement.
제가 그 글을 올린 지 얼마나 됐나요? 세용 씨는 아직 공식적인 입장도 내지 않고 있습니다.
sorry
죄송합니다
This is all I can say now
지금 내가 할 수 있는 말은 이것뿐이다
(Se Yong)
(세용)
If this continues, we will all be fired, right?
계속 이러면 우리 다 해고되겠죠?
Then take the legal route
그럼 합법적인 길로 가세요
correct
옳은
Your mother is a judge, right?
네 엄마가 판사지?
Why are you saying this suddenly?
갑자기 왜 이런 말을 하는 걸까요?
Then she must know many relevant people in the legal field
그렇다면 그녀는 법률 분야의 관련 사람들을 많이 알아야 합니다.
At least it will be beneficial to us in the lawsuit
적어도 소송에서는 우리에게 도움이 될 것입니다
My mother should know a lot of people
우리 엄마는 사람을 많이 알아야 해
but I do not have
하지만 난 없어
Yes, you have a bad relationship with your mother
응, 너 엄마랑 사이가 안 좋아.
Yes, we don’t have a good relationship, and we haven’t seen each other for a long time.
네, 우리는 사이가 좋지 않고 오랫동안 보지도 못했습니다.
Every time your mother is mentioned, you lose your temper
네 엄마가 언급될 때마다 너는 화를 낸다.
how about you?
당신은 어떤가요?
You still refuse to call her mother
당신은 아직도 그녀의 어머니에게 전화하기를 거부합니다
My situation is different from yours
내 상황은 너랑 달라
Don't compare you to me
당신을 나와 비교하지 마세요
Yeah, your situation is worse than mine, bleak and miserable.
네, 당신의 상황은 나보다 더 나쁘고, 암울하고 비참합니다.
-Are you satisfied? -When you said that, I felt worse again.
- 만족하시나요? -그렇게 말하니 또 기분이 나빠졌어요.
It's time to prepare
이제 준비할 시간이다
Are you relaxing now?
지금은 쉬고 있나요?
Absolutely not
절대적으로하지
Before convening the personnel committee of Deputy Yoo Jae-min and Deputy Park Yoon-so
유재민 대리 , 박윤소 대리 인사위원회 소집 전
There's something I need to confirm first
먼저 확인하고 싶은 게 있어요
It’s about the launch process of protein powder products with upgraded formulas
업그레이드된 제형의 단백질분말 제품 출시과정 에 관한 내용입니다.
What does that have to do with the case being heard by the Personnel Committee today ?
그것이 오늘 인사위원회에서 심리되는 사건과 무슨 관련이 있습니까 ?
Manufacturers supplying protein powder raw materials have made changes
단백질 분말 원료를 공급하는 제조업체가 변경되었습니다.
I think you all should know
다들 아셔야 할 것 같아요
Switched from Dongshin to PF
동신에서 PF로 전환
And this new manufacturer
그리고 이 새로운 제조사는
It's a company run by a relative of Zhao Zhenrui, the leader of the sales team.
영업팀장인 Zhao Zhenrui의 친척이 운영하는 회사입니다.
Whether it is factory facilities, manpower or R&D capabilities
공장 시설이든, 인력이든, R&D 능력이든
They are extremely backward in every aspect and are a messed up company.
그들은 모든 면에서 매우 낙후되어 있고 엉망인 회사입니다.
Therefore, defective products are an expected result
따라서 불량제품은 당연한 결과입니다
Moreover, when there are already victims
게다가 이미 피해자가 있는 경우에는
They even teamed up with each other to cover it up
심지어 이를 은폐하기 위해 서로 팀을 이루기도 했습니다.
What on earth are you talking about?
도대체 무슨 말을 하는 거야?
-You like playing golf, right? -What?
- 골프를 좋아하시죠? -무엇?
It's just a simple question
그냥 간단한 질문이에요
Do you like to play golf?
당신은 골프를 좋아합니까?
(One day before the personnel committee meeting)
(인사위원회 회의 하루 전)
You are here, but why are you here?
당신은 여기에 있는데 왜 여기에 있습니까?
Can we have a chat?
우리 얘기 좀 할 수 있을까요?
i have been thinking
나는 생각해왔다
“ What is Team Leader Song Xuantai’s stance on this matter?
“ 이 문제에 대한 송쉬안타이 팀장은 어떤 입장을 가지고 있나요?
How deeply involved is he with Team Leader Zhao's corruption?
그는 자오 팀장의 비리와 얼마나 깊이 연관되어 있습니까?
Does he have no idea, or is he just...
그 사람은 전혀 모르는 걸까요, 아니면 그냥...
The core figure in this corruption incident?
이번 비리 사건의 핵심인물은?
If not, does he play the role of a ghost in this round? "
그렇지 않다면 이번 라운드에서 그는 유령 역할을 하게 될까요? "
All right
괜찮은
maybe you don't know
어쩌면 당신은 모를 수도 있어요
The ingredient analysis sheet that I handed over...
건네준 성분분석표..
is fake
가짜다
If you just accept the analysis table given by Team Leader Zhao
자오팀장이 알려주는 분석표 만 받아들이면
Although Team Leader Zhao is from the same hometown as you,
자오 팀장은 당신과 같은 고향 출신이지만,
I'm also a junior from the same school as you.
나도 너랑 같은 학교 후배야.
But you may have nothing to do with Team Leader Zhao’s corruption.
하지만 당신은 자오 팀장의 비리와 아무 관련이 없을 수도 있습니다 .
right
오른쪽
I might think so
그렇게 생각할 수도 있겠네요
but
하지만
This seems unjustifiable to anyone.
이것은 누구에게도 정당화될 수 없는 것처럼 보입니다.
Especially someone like Se Yong
특히 세용같은 사람은
Relying on personal connections and alumni relationships to build bridges
개인적인 인맥과 동문 관계를 활용하여 가교를 쌓습니다.
support each other
서로를 지원하다
This is especially true for companies that provide help
이는 도움을 제공하는 회사의 경우 특히 그렇습니다.
Director Gu…
구 감독…
It was Chief Chen and Chief Larkin who set up the trap.
함정을 설치한 것은 첸 추장과 라킨 추장이었다.
And you are the middleman who helps match up Director Chen and Team Leader Zhao, right?
그리고 첸 이사님과 자오 팀장 연결을 도와주시는 중개인이시죠 ?
That's the heart of this protein powder scandal
이것이 바로 이 단백질 파우더 스캔들의 핵심입니다
It is also the origin of all events
모든 사건의 근원이기도 하다
you hope to
당신은 희망
What do I do?
어떻게 해야 하나요?
Do you want me to be an inside whistleblower?
제가 내부 고발자가 되기를 바라시나요?
I…
나…
I look down on that kind of person
나는 그런 사람을 얕본다
Team Leader Song
송팀장
Don't sink with the boat under your feet
배를 발 밑에 두고 가라앉지 말라
Let's switch to another ship as soon as possible
빨리 다른 배로 바꾸자
Times have changed now
이제 시대가 바뀌었어요
It doesn't matter even if you do that
그렇게 해도 상관은 없어
"Agent Song Xuantai who helped Section Chief Chen Bingwan cover up the crime of accepting bribes"
"천빙완 과장의 뇌물 수수 범죄를 은폐하는 데 도움을 준 송쉬안타이 요원"
You have to break away from this relationship
이 관계에서 벗어나야 해
Stop letting your past life determine your worth
과거의 삶이 당신의 가치를 결정하도록 두지 마세요
Let it be reflected in Seyong’s future
세용이의 미래에 반영되길
You will know after reading it, currently replacing Dongxin
읽어보시면 아시겠지만 현재 Dongxin을 대체하고 있습니다.
The raw materials are provided by PF Factory, a company run by a relative of team leader Zhao Zhenrui.
원자재는 팀 리더 Zhao Zhenrui의 친척이 운영하는 회사인 PF Factory에서 제공됩니다.
As far as I know, President Park Ji-hoon of PF will provide
제가 아는 한 PF 박지훈 회장이
Golf membership coupons and cars are given to the head of the finance department and office manager Chen in return.
이에 대한 보답으로 재무부서장과 첸 사무장에게 골프회원권과 자동차 등을 증정한다.
Sorry for not informing you in advance
미리 공지드리지 못해 죄송합니다
Chief Kim, do you have the membership coupon for Lucun CC?
김실장님, 루쿤CC 회원쿠폰 가지고 계시나요?
Chief Chen has membership coupons for Eastern Benister
Chen 과장은 Eastern Benister 회원 쿠폰을 가지고 있습니다.
Yeochon CC’s membership coupons are worth 1.8 billion won
여촌CC 회원쿠폰 가치는 18억 원
Dongbu Benister’s membership coupons are worth 980 million won
동부베니스터 멤버십 쿠폰은 9억8천만원 상당
Stop talking about irrelevant things!
쓸데없는 얘기는 이제 그만!
Drag that woman out
그 여자를 끌어내라
The person who presented the membership coupon was none other than President Park Ji-hoon of raw material manufacturer PF.
멤버십 쿠폰을 제시한 사람은 바로 원자재 제조업체 PF의 박지훈 사장이었다.
And he is also the brother-in-law of Zhao Zhenrui, the leader of the sales team.
그리고 그는 영업팀장 인 Zhao Zhenrui의 처남 이기도 합니다 .
I said drag that woman out
그 여자를 끌어내라고 했어
Take away that woman who is talking nonsense!
말도 안되는 소리하는 여자를 데려가세요!
Drag that woman out quickly!
그 여자를 빨리 끌어내라!
Didn't you hear what I said?
내가 한 말 못 들었어?
You like more than just golf
당신은 골프 그 이상을 좋아합니다
You also like cars and luxury resorts
당신은 또한 자동차와 고급 리조트를 좋아합니다
-enough - cash of course
- 충분하다 - 물론 현금
Shut up!
입 다물어!
vice president
부사장
I have dedicated my whole life to Shirong
나는 시롱에게 평생을 바쳤습니다.
You should know very well
당신은 아주 잘 알고 있어야합니다
Don't you know?
모르시나요?
I gave it my all!
나는 내 모든 것을 바쳤다!
Is it just me?
나 뿐인가요?
No
아니요
Inspection team
검사팀
-Please investigate this matter thoroughly -Yes
- 이 문제를 철저히 조사해 주십시오 . - 예
Is there anything you two want to say?
두 분 하고 싶은 말씀 있으신가요?
I don't
나는 아니에요
I…
나…
I have never been ashamed of Shi Rong
나는 시롱을 부끄러워한 적이 없다.
But that’s not because Shirong is really acting magnanimously.
하지만 시롱이 정말 늠름하게 행동해서 그런 건 아니다.
It's because I have no expectations for the company
회사에 기대가 없기 때문이에요
But this colleague next to me
그런데 내 옆에 있는 이 동료는
During the implementation of this project
이 프로젝트를 실행하는 동안
I really blamed myself countless times
정말 수없이 자책했어
Blaming myself for not objecting more actively
좀 더 적극적으로 반대하지 못한 나 자신을 탓한다.
she is very remorseful
그녀는 매우 후회하고 있어요
See her like that
그녀를 그렇게 봐
i feel ashamed of myself
나 자신이 부끄럽다
I also realized that I have been doing nothing
나도 내가 아무것도 하지 않았다는 걸 깨달았어
It is also part of the reason why Shirong culture is so outdated and unreasonable.
시롱문화 가 낡고 불합리한 이유이기도 하다 .
So I plan to change starting with me
그래서 나부터 변하려고 해
I decided to look forward to it
나는 그것을 기대하기로 결정했다
That's all I want to say
그게 내가 말하고 싶은 전부야
you first
당신이 먼저
You told me the problem was
당신은 나에게 문제가 있다고 말했어요
Serong’s corporate culture, right?
세롱이의 기업문화죠?
right
오른쪽
Can that change overnight?
하루아침에 바뀔 수 있나요?
Although not that fast
그렇게 빠르진 않아도
But it seems to have begun to change
하지만 점점 변하기 시작한 것 같아
Yeah?
응?
About internal culture improvement plan
내부 문화 개선 계획에 대해
you have to take responsibility
당신은 책임을 져야합니다
Complete the plan well
계획을 잘 완성해라
yes
예
Thanks a lot
정말 감사합니다
You were so handsome just now
방금 너 정말 잘생겼었어
It's because you are handsome
네가 잘생겼기 때문이야
all because of you
모든게 너 때문이야
It's all thanks to you that I had that thought
그런 생각을 갖게 된 건 다 네 덕분이야
Really, please take that line back
정말로, 그 대사를 취소해주세요
I'm getting goosebumps
소름이 돋네
By the way, that golf course membership ticket?
그런데 그 골프장 회원권?
How did Director Goo know?
구 감독은 어떻게 알았나?
She even knows the price clearly
그녀는 가격까지 확실히 알고 있어요
There must be someone inside helping her
안에 그녀를 돕는 누군가가 있을 거에요
Could it be Team Leader Song?
송 팀장 아닐까요?
impossible
불가능한
not him
그는 아니고
Could it be him?
그 사람이 아닐까?
Didn't the vice president just order a thorough investigation?
부통령이 방금 철저한 수사를 지시한 게 아니었나요?
If Team Leader Song does something wrong, he will definitely be found out.
송팀장이 잘못하면 반드시 밝혀지겠죠.
Yes, you are right
그래 네가 맞아
You should have a drink today
오늘은 한잔 해야지
I have an appointment
약속이 있어요
Are you planning to officially start a relationship?
공식적으로 연애를 시작할 계획인가요?
Yes, probably
네 아마도
Do you like…
당신은 좋아합니까?
That person?
저 사람?
right
오른쪽
I like him, he is a good man
나는 그 사람을 좋아해요, 그는 좋은 사람이에요
That's enough
충분 해
You ask me how to tell whether it is friendship or love?
우정인지 사랑인지 어떻게 알 수 있는지 물어보시나요 ?
Because even if you are a friend , you might like her very much.
왜냐하면 당신이 친구라 할지라도 당신은 그녀를 매우 좋아할 수도 있기 때문입니다.
Aren't you confused with love?
사랑과 헷갈리지 않나요?
Are you stupid? How could there be confusion?
너 바 보니? 어떻게 혼란이 있을 수 있겠습니까?
is that so?
그렇습니까?
Otherwise, try to think about whether you would want to kiss or sleep with her.
그렇지 않다면 그녀와 키스하고 싶은지, 자고 싶은지 생각해 보세요 .
Let’s see if you can do it or not
당신이 할 수 있는지 없는지 봅시다
Then there's the answer
그럼 답이 나와있어요
What's wrong? who is it?
뭐가 문제 야? 누구야?
Among the friends you know...
아는 친구들 중에..
No way?
안 돼요?
What?
무엇?
Could it be...
그럴 수도 있지...
Reporter Choi, right?
최 기자 맞죠?
Damn, things get complicated.
젠장, 상황이 복잡해지네요.
you…
너…
Huiying confessed to you
후이잉이 너한테 고백했어
-What? -She's exactly your type, right?
-무엇? - 그 사람 딱 당신 타입이거든요, 그렇죠?
Hey, get out of here after drinking the wine
야, 와인 마시고 여기서 나가
I really can't stand you
난 정말 당신을 참을 수 없어
If not Reporter Choi, then who?
최 기자가 아니면 누구?
Actually it is...
실제로 그것은 ...
you
너
Neuropathy
신경 장해
you crazy
너 미쳤어
Is it Yun Zhao?
자오윤인가?
The meat is super soft and almost melts in your mouth
고기가 엄청 부드러워서 입에서 녹을 것 같은 느낌
Not to that point yet
아직 그 정도까지는 아니야
Don't pick on my bad language, I'm just saying the meat is delicious
욕하지마세요 그냥 고기가 맛있다는 말이에요
good
좋은
This meal is mine
이 식사는 내꺼야
Representative, enjoy it.
대표님, 맛있게 드세요.
I treat you because I want to thank you
감사하다는 마음으로 대접합니다
But can you please stop calling me representative?
그런데 저를 대표라고 부르지 말아 주실 수 있나요?
This title is too standard
제목이 너무 평범해요
How about calling you "honey"?
"여보"라고 부르는 게 어때요?
I'm just kidding
장난이야
It's too exaggerated to call it that.
그렇게 부르기에는 너무 과장됐다.
What about "baby"?
"아기"는 어떻습니까?
What?
무엇?
How can we call you that when we have no relationship ?
우리가 아무 관계도 없는데 어떻게 당신을 그렇게 부를 수 있나요 ?
Didn't we have a relationship?
우리 관계가 아니었나요?
Have we dated?
우리 데이트했어요?
When did it start?
그건 언제 시작 했습니까?
Then let’s start dating from today. Today is the first day.
그럼 오늘부터 연애를 시작하자 오늘이 첫 날이다.
Isn't it time yet?
아직 시간이 되지 않았나요?
Do you need a little more time?
시간이 조금 더 필요합니까?
But I can't seem to wait any longer
하지만 더 이상은 기다릴 수 없을 것 같아
Am I being a bit selfish?
제가 좀 이기적인가요?
Is that your answer?
그게 당신의 대답인가요?
This answer is a bit unsettling
이 답변은 좀 불안하네요
Does this mean I need to have a good cry when I get home?
이것은 내가 집에 갈 때 잘 울어야 한다는 뜻인가요?
So
그래서
Today is the first day of our relationship
오늘은 우리 관계의 첫날이야
Are you negotiating?
협상 중인가요?
You can also refuse
거절할 수도 있다
All right
괜찮은
After all, it feels like I like you more
결국엔 내가 더 좋아하는 것 같아
make a deal
거래를하다
- over there - okay
- 저기 - 알았어
(American Chinatown snacks)
(미국 차이나타운 스낵)
-Right? -right
-오른쪽? -오른쪽
That’s right…
좋아요…
- they were a little panicked - um
- 조금 당황했어요 - 네.
You want me to apologize publicly?
공개적으로 사과하라고요?
right
오른쪽
You must bend down and apologize in person
몸을 굽혀 직접 사과해야 한다
In Korea, you may lose your job because of a hidden ad
한국에서는 숨겨진 광고 때문에 일자리를 잃을 수도 있다
But we are using social media to spread false news in South Korea
하지만 우리는 소셜 미디어를 이용해 한국에 거짓 뉴스를 퍼뜨리고 있습니다.
Therefore we need a sincere apology from the company representative
그러므로 회사 대표님의 진심어린 사과가 필요합니다.
no problem
괜찮아요
correct
옳은
You also have to talk about the internal cons
내부적인 단점도 이야기해야 합니다.
Do we need to expose our company's scandals to the public one by one?
우리 회사의 스캔들을 하나씩 대중에게 공개해야 합니까 ?
You can't just apologize
사과만 하면 안 돼
You must also demonstrate your responsible attitude as a representative
대표자로서 책임감 있는 태도 도 보여야 합니다.
So we can't hide anything anymore
그러니까 우리는 더 이상 아무것도 숨길 수 없어
Then let's make a public apology.
그럼 공개 사과를 합시다.
I was busy dealing with the Human Resources Committee, so the response was slow.
인사위원회 업무로 바쁜 관계로 답변이 느렸습니다.
I'm sorry about that
그 점은 죄송해요
I knew I chose the golden axe
난 내가 황금도끼를 선택했다는 걸 알았어
instead of a bad ax
나쁜 도끼 대신
us
우리를
I sincerely apologize to you
진심으로 사과드립니다
We will definitely try our best
우리는 반드시 최선을 다할 것입니다
Don't let this happen again
이런 일이 다시는 발생하지 않도록 하세요
Shi Yong Hui strives to become a company that fulfills corporate social responsibilities
시용희는 기업의 사회적 책임을 다하는 기업이 되기 위해 노력합니다.
We apologize again
다시한번 사과드립니다
I am Se Rong’s representative, Lin Zhixian
저는 세롱의 대표 Lin Zhixian 입니다
first
첫 번째
Regarding the recent controversy caused by our company’s protein powder products
최근 당사 단백질분말 제품 으로 인한 논란 에 대하여
caused concern among the people
국민들 사이에 우려를 불러일으켰다
I would like to express my deepest apologies for this
이에 대해 깊은 사과의 말씀을 드리고 싶습니다.
We are conducting thorough internal monitoring
철저한 내부 모니터링을 실시하고 있습니다.
Try to find out the exact cause so you can take follow-up measures
후속 조치를 취할 수 있도록 정확한 원인을 찾아보십시오.
Based on the results of internal monitoring
내부 모니터링 결과를 바탕으로
We found that within the company
우리는 회사 내에서 그것을 발견했습니다
Major problems occurred during the communication process
의사소통 과정에서 발생한 주요 문제
we have not reflected
우리는 반영하지 않았습니다
A routine of repeating past mistakes
과거의 실수를 반복하는 루틴
I think this kind of thing should never happen
이런 일은 절대 있어서는 안 될 것 같아요
In addition, for the failure to thoroughly confirm in advance
그 밖에 사전에 충분히 확인하지 못한 경우
Product safety lapses
제품 안전 실패
Even if it’s just once…
단 한 번이라도…
I went to see her
나는 그녀를 만나러 갔다
No forgiveness either
용서도 안돼
The woman in the picture just now
지금 사진 속 여자
To prevent similar incidents from happening again
비슷한 사건이 다시는 발생하지 않도록
We will significantly improve the way we communicate with the outside world
우리는 외부 세계와 소통하는 방식을 크게 개선할 것입니다.
- Sit down for a moment - Shi Rong played a good chess game
- 잠시 앉아보세요 - 시롱이 체스를 잘 두었어요
Can it be reversed?
되돌릴 수 있나요?
The current public opinion of the people is lukewarm, attracting public attention
현재 국민 여론은 미온적이어서 세간의 주목을 받고 있다.
So what do you want to do?
그럼 당신은 무엇을 하고 싶나요?
I shouldn't have gone to see her
난 그녀를 만나러 가지 말았어야 했어
After meeting her, I realized that even though I hate her
그 사람을 만나고 나서야 깨달았어, 내가 그 사람을 미워해도
But I also miss her very much
하지만 나도 그녀가 너무 그리워요
I feel a little sorry for you
너한테 좀 미안한 마음이 들어
Why do you feel sorry for me?
왜 나를 불쌍히 여기나요?
Aren't you still angry with her?
당신은 아직도 그 사람에게 화가 나지 않나요?
Because she left us and walked away
그 사람이 우리를 버리고 떠났기 때문에
I know exactly how you feel
난 당신이 어떤 기분인지 정확히 알아요
so
그래서
When I start to miss her a little
그녀가 조금 그리워지기 시작하면
will feel guilty
죄책감을 느낄 것이다
I didn't mean to hide it from you
너한테 숨길 생각은 없었어
It's just that I don't feel comfortable lying all the time.
단지 나는 항상 거짓말을 하는 것이 불편할 뿐입니다.
Yu Zhen
유 젠
First of all, I appreciate you telling me honestly
우선 솔직하게 말씀해주셔서 감사해요
What do you think of your mother?
어머니에 대해 어떻게 생각하세요?
But I hope you don't feel guilty about me
하지만 나에 대해 죄책감을 느끼지 않기를 바랍니다.
Whatever feelings you have for her, that's up to you.
그녀에 대한 당신의 감정이 무엇이든 그것은 당신에게 달려 있습니다.
And I will respect you
그리고 나는 당신을 존경할 것입니다
thanks for saying that
그렇게 말해줘서 고마워
Then I'll go back to the room
그럼 난 방으로 돌아갈게
I can do it too…
나도 할 수 있어…
Trying to see
보려고 노력 중
Although not sure what the outcome will be
비록 결과가 어떻게 될지는 확실하지 않지만
Why are you looking for me?
왜 나를 찾고 있나요?
Is there a problem?
문제가 있습니까?
Have you heard about me?
나에 대해 들어본 적 있나요?
What's up?
무슨 일이야?
I'm getting ready to run for mayor.
저는 시장 출마를 준비하고 있습니다.
But I have to win the party primary first
하지만 먼저 당 경선에서 이겨야 해
It turned out to be this
이것이 밝혀졌습니다
Why don't you help me?
왜 나를 도와주지 않습니까?
What are you doing? Do you want to ask me for help now or what?
뭐하세요? 지금 나에게 도움을 요청하고 싶나요 ?
This is not a request, but a proposal
이건 부탁이 아니라 제안이에요
Many people recommend you to me
많은 분들이 추천해 주셨는데요
And I can't completely ignore it
그리고 나는 그것을 완전히 무시할 수 없습니다
I see
알겠어요
I reject your proposal
나는 당신의 제안을 거부합니다
I'm not happy at all
나는 전혀 행복하지 않다
Yeah?
응?
I originally wanted to see your ability
원래는 네 능력을 보고 싶었어
Anyway, I gave you another chance
어쨌든 난 너에게 다시 한번 기회를 줬어
You are the one who is dismissive
당신은 무시하는 사람입니다
This conclusion really fits your style
이 결론은 당신의 스타일에 정말 적합합니다
Okay, I think we're done talking, so I'll leave first.
알았어, 얘기는 끝난 것 같으니 나 먼저 갈게.
Thank you for taking the time to stop by
시간을 내서 들러주셔서 감사합니다
that's all?
그게 다야?
It seems you have other expectations
다른 기대도 있는 것 같은데
Is it about Yu Zhen?
Yu Zhen에 관한 것인가요?
What a shame, I have nothing to say
참 부끄러워서 할말이 없네
It seems you guessed wrong
추측이 잘못된 것 같습니다.
If I'm not mistaken, I won't come at all
내가 착각하지 않으면 전혀 오지 않을 것이다
(Ahn Eun-seok)
(안은석)
(Cheongdam cram school)
(청담학원)
(Se Yong)
(세용)
Speaking of Team Leader Song
송 팀장에 대해 말하자면
It is said that he helped cover up all of Team Leader Zhao’s illegal activities.
자오팀장의 불법행위를 모두 은폐하는데 도움을 주었다고 한다.
In exchange for a death-free gold medal
무사 금메달의 대가로
Think about it, his child is in Australia
생각해보세요. 그의 아이는 호주에 있어요
Then he must have gained something from Team Leader Zhao , right?
그렇다면 자오팀장에게서 뭔가 얻은 게 있지 않을까요?
-Maybe not. -I was shocked.
- 아닐 수도 있어요 - 충격받았어요
Why do you show up silently every time?
왜 매번 조용히 나타나나요?
I think Team Leader Song
송 팀장인 것 같아요.
Maybe not that kind of person
그런 사람은 아닐지도 몰라
Are you crazy? Why speak for him?
제정신이에요? 왜 그를 대신해서 말해야 합니까?
no
아니요
I just feel that way
그냥 그런 느낌이에요
You just…
방금…
Just think about yourself
그냥 너 자신에 대해 생각해봐
No one will help you at all
아무도 당신을 전혀 도와주지 않을 거예요
so
그래서
Just protect yourself
그냥 자신을 보호
Maybe he was acting so strong to protect himself
어쩌면 그는 자신을 보호하기 위해 너무 강한 행동을 했을 수도 있습니다.
Do you have a high fever?
열이 많이 나나요?
-Brother -Hmm
-오빠 -흠
Her brain is burned out and she's talking nonsense
그녀의 뇌는 타버렸고 그녀는 말도 안되는 소리를 하고 있어요
Then she needs to be hospitalized
그럼 그 사람은 입원해야 해
Is it 119?
119인가요?
There's a guy here who's talking crazy nonsense
여기 말도 안 되는 소리를 하는 남자가 있어요
wait a minute
잠깐 기다려요
My body temperature is even higher
내 체온은 더 높아
Because I'm angry
화가 나니까
Please actively participate in the internal culture improvement plan survey
내부문화 개선방안 설문조사 에 적극 참여해 주시기 바랍니다.
Thanks
감사해요
Only your attention can change the world
당신의 관심만이 세상을 바꿀 수 있습니다
If you have anything you don’t understand or have other questions, you can ask me.
이해가 안 되는 부분이나 다른 질문이 있으면 저에게 물어보세요.
You can also fill out the questionnaire online
온라인으로 설문지를 작성할 수도 있습니다.
(Please participate in the Internal Culture Improvement Plan Survey!)
(내부문화 개선방안 설문조사에 꼭 참여해주세요!)
(1. Evaluation system)
(1. 평가제도)
(Seyong Internal Culture Improvement Plan Questionnaire)
(세용 내부 문화 개선 계획 설문지)
( How important do you think it is to set key performance indicators?)
( 핵심성과지표를 설정하는 것이 얼마나 중요하다고 생각하시나요?)
(2. Internal company culture)
(2. 내부 기업문화)
(Results of internal culture improvement questionnaire)
(내부문화 개선 설문조사 결과)
(How satisfied are you with the culture within your company currently ?)
(현재 회사 내 문화에 얼마나 만족하시나요 ?)
( How important do you think it is to set key performance indicators?)
( 핵심성과지표를 설정하는 것이 얼마나 중요하다고 생각하시나요?)
(Do you think you can communicate effectively with the team leader?)
( 팀장과 효과적으로 소통 할 수 있다고 생각하시나요 ?)
(can communicate effectively, can communicate well, cannot communicate)
(효과적으로 의사소통을 할 수 있다, 의사소통을 잘 할 수 있다, 의사소통을 할 수 없다)
Come on, Yun Zhao
자, 윤자오
Then Seung Hee...
그럼 승희..
in my opinion…
내 생각에는…
this…
이것…
The next item is
다음 항목은
Fair evaluation based on work results
업무결과에 따른 공정한 평가
The method is to select the score that suits the individual from one point to ten points.
1점부터 10점까지 개인에게 맞는 점수를 선택하는 방식입니다 .
This is a list of systems they hope to introduce in the future
앞으로 도입하고 싶은 시스템 목록은 다음과 같습니다.
This is much better than I expected
이건 내가 기대했던 것보다 훨씬 낫네
Thanks a lot
정말 감사합니다
-Dinner together!
-저녁 같이 먹자!
-No problem, let's go
- 문제없어, 가자
Hello, Team Leader Liu
안녕하세요, 류팀장님
Are you here to visit, you brat? He actually sat there and didn't help.
방문하러 왔나요, 이 자식아? 그는 실제로 거기 앉아서 도움을 주지 않았습니다.
Agent Park is left busy all by himself.
박요원은 혼자 바쁘다.
what happened again? That girl is better than me
또 무슨 일이 일어난 거야? 그 여자가 나보다 더 나아
"That girl"?
"그 소녀"?
what? Is this place filled with pink bubbles too?
무엇? 이곳에도 핑크빛 비눗방울이 가득하죠?
Sure enough, it’s better to be single, you can have ambiguities everywhere
역시 싱글이 낫지 어디든 모호함은 있을 수 있지
Everyone, I have a boyfriend, okay?
여러분 저 남자친구 있어요 알죠?
Now it's time to reveal
이제 공개할 시간이다
Liu Caimin was my classmate in elementary school and junior high school.
유채민은 저의 초등학교, 중학교 동창이었습니다.
OK, I'll say it again
알았어, 다시 말할게
This girl is better than me
이 여자가 나보다 낫다
What's there to hide?
숨길 게 뭐가 있나요?
scared me
날 무섭게했다
If you completely fooled us, then it's obviously no big deal.
당신이 우리를 완전히 속였다면 그것은 분명히 별 일이 아닙니다.
Then help arrange things quickly. Director Gu will be here soon.
그럼 빨리 정리를 도와주세요. 구 부장님이 곧 오실 겁니다.
OK, I'll help set it up
알겠습니다. 설정을 도와드리겠습니다
By the way, I heard that both Chief Kim and Chief Chen have resigned.
그런데 김 실장 과 첸 실장이 모두 사임했다는 소식을 들었습니다.
They mentioned it before the inspection results came out.
검사 결과가 나오기 전에 언급한 거죠.
What about Team Leader Song?
송 팀장은 어떻습니까?
He seems to have been under surveillance together , but I don’t know what the outcome will be.
같이 감시를 받고 있었던 것 같은데 , 결과는 어떻게 될지 모르겠습니다.
I'm really curious
정말 궁금해요
What role did he play?
그는 어떤 역할을 했나요?
Team leader Zhao also resigned, right?
자오 팀장도 사임했지요?
How could it be just him?
어떻게 그 사람 일 수 있니?
Those who knew the truth about the victimization in advance but remained silent
피해 사실을 사전에 알고도 침묵을 지킨 이들
Also assisted the person responsible for falsifying information
또한 정보를 위조한 책임자를 도왔습니다.
They were all fired one by one.
그들은 모두 하나씩 해고되었습니다.
correct
옳은
Were all the people in charge of the protein powder case in the public relations office having their salaries cut?
홍보실 단백질분말 사건 담당자들은 모두 급여가 삭감됐나요?
After all, we made a mistake and we have to accept it calmly.
결국 우리는 실수를 했고 그것을 침착하게 받아들여야 한다.
Director Goo is here!
구 감독님이 오셨어요!
-Director Goo!
- 구 감독님!
-welcome!
-환영!
-The presentation is beautiful. -Welcome
-프레젠테이션이 아름답습니다 .
Celebrate with champagne
샴페인으로 축하하기
Why do you carry so many bottles?
왜 그렇게 많은 병을 가지고 다니나요?
-How many bottles are there in total? -How many bottles did you bring?
- 총 몇 병이 있나요? -몇 병을 가져왔나요?
Thanks
감사해요
-Thank you, Director Goo -Thank you
-고맙습니다, 구감독님 .
-Thank you for your hard work, everyone .
- 모두들 고생 많으 셨습니다 .
Thanks
감사해요
-cheers!
- 건배!
Thanks for your hard work!
당신의 노고에 감사드립니다!
-Thank you for your hard work . -Thank you for your hard work.
- 수고해 주셔서 감사합니다 . - 수고해 주셔서 감사합니다.
- Well done. - Good job.
- 잘했어요
-It's so delicious. -How does it taste?
- 너무 맛있어요 - 맛이 어때요?
Very delicious
아주 맛있는
That, Director Goo
그거, 구 감독님
Maybe you feel a little panicked
어쩌면 당신은 약간 당황한 느낌이 들 수도 있습니다.
But I really have something to tell you
그런데 정말 할 말이 있어요
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
I think
제 생각에는
become someone like you
너 같은 사람이 되어라
If it's not too late
너무 늦지 않았다면
That won't work
작동하지 않습니다
I think so
그렇게 생각해요
Yes, that's right, I was overestimating my abilities.
그래, 맞아, 나는 내 능력을 과대평가하고 있었다.
you have to be a better person
너는 더 나은 사람이 되어야 해
a better person than me
나보다 나은 사람
What a great day today
오늘 정말 좋은 날이네요
I'm really your fan
나는 정말로 당신의 팬이에요
If you don't mind, could you sign it for me?
괜찮으시면 저 대신 서명해 주시겠어요?
-sign? -right
-징후? -오른쪽
What? Are you kidding me?
무엇? 농담하는 거야?
No, I'm 100% serious
아니요, 저는 100% 진심이에요
Oh my god
맙소사
Oh my God, how did you get this photo?
맙소사, 이 사진은 어떻게 구하셨나요?
OMG
어머나
"To Yun Zhao"
"자오윤에게"
Thank you
감사합니다
Oh my god
맙소사
(Outline of Organizational Adjustment Case)
(조직조정 사례의 개요)
(Communications Department, Organizational Adjustment Case)
(소통부, 조직조정 사건)
Are you sure the vice president will really agree to this?
부통령이 정말로 이에 동의할 것이라고 확신하시나요?
He has no reason to stop
그 사람은 멈출 이유가 없어
Forget it, vice president
잊어버리세요, 부사장님
What about Zheng Shouhuan?
정수환은 어떻습니까?
Oh my god
맙소사
This is really innovative...
이거 정말 혁신적이네요...
At least be the head of the sales department
최소한 영업부서장이라도 돼라
Isn't it more suitable for you than the head of the Strategy Headquarters?
전략본부장보다 더 어울리지 않나요?
(Outline of Organizational Adjustment Case)
(조직조정 사례의 개요)
(Public Relations Group, Team Leader, Cui Yonghao)
(홍보그룹 최용하오 팀장)
Who put this?
이거 누가 넣었어?
(Application form for early retirement)
(조기퇴직 신청서)
(I plan to apply for voluntary retirement due to company business reasons, please approve)
( 회사 업무상 이유로 희망퇴직을 신청할 예정이오니, 승인부탁드립니다)
(Announcement, 2023 organizational adjustment plan)
(공고, 2023년 조직조정계획)
(Communications Department, Head of Department Goo Yi-jung)
(커뮤니케이션부 구이정 과장)
(Business Department, Department Chief Zheng Qiurong)
(사업부, 부서장 Zheng Qiurong)
Alas, I saved you, these brats
아아 내가 구했어 이 새끼들아
Especially the one over there , he really needs to be grateful to me.
특히 저쪽에 있는 사람은 나에게 정말 감사해야 해요.
Hey, what's going on? Please explain
이봐 무슨 일이야? 설명 해주십시오
The company has established a new communications department
회사는 새로운 커뮤니케이션 부서를 설립했습니다
There is a communications department and a strategy department underneath.
그 아래에는 커뮤니케이션 부서와 전략 부서가 있습니다.
The head of the communications department is Director Goo?
통신부장은 구국장?
Hey, the PR team and the marketing team have merged.
안녕하세요, 홍보팀과 마케팅팀이 합쳐졌습니다.
Several employees from the Strategy Office and Human Resources Office were also transferred here.
전략실과 인사실 직원도 이곳으로 전근됐다 .
(2023 Serong Human Resources Appointment, Staff)
(2023년 세롱인재 임용, 직원)
(Personnel appointment)
(인사)
Hello, I'm in the communications department's group
안녕하세요 커뮤니케이션팀입니다
oh? Me too
오? 저도요
(Ryu Jae-min, one group of broadcasters and Park Yun-soo, one group of broadcasters)
(방송인 1군 류재민 과 방송인 1인 박윤수)
(Kim Houji, Lee Seung-hee)
(김호지, 이승희)
(Communication Group 3, Agent)
(통신3그룹, 상담원)
The pool leader is a group leader
풀 리더는 그룹 리더입니다.
The leader of the second group is the leader of the marketing group. As for the leader of the third group
두 번째 그룹의 리더는 마케팅 그룹의 리더가 되고, 세 번째 그룹의 리더는
It seems to be hired from outside, and it’s an unknown name.
외부에서 고용한 것 같은데, 이름은 불명.
Section Chief Meng is also in the same group.
맹 과장도 같은 그룹에 속해 있다.
We are in the same group
우리는 같은 그룹에 속해 있어요
Hello
안녕하세요
Agent Liu, you have been promoted to section chief.
Liu 요원, 당신은 과장으로 승진했습니다.
congratulations
축하해요
Hey, it’s true. Congratulations.
아 맞네요 축하드립니다.
Oh my gosh, Seung Hee, you’ve been promoted to agent too
맙소사 승희님도 에이전트로 승진하셨네요
yes!
예!
(SeRong HR appoints senior managers in 2023)
(세롱인재는 2023년 고위관리자를 선임한다)
Team Leader Song…
송 팀장…
(Song Xuantai, Head of Department)
(부서장 송쉬안타이)
He was promoted to executive
그는 임원으로 승진했다.
He also became the head of the communications department
그는 또한 커뮤니케이션 부서의 책임자가 되었습니다.
Senior, congratulations
선배님, 축하드립니다
Song Changzhu
송창주
-Congratulations -Thank you
-축하해요 - 감사합니다
Congratulations so much
정말 축하해요
- Seung Hee, congratulations. - Congratulations.
- 승희야, 축하해 - 축하해
-Congratulations. -Thank you so much.
-축하해요 - 정말 고마워요
-I will be loyal to you for the rest of my life -Hey
-평생 당신에게 충성하겠습니다 .
Congratulations on your promotion. You are now Section Chief Liu.
승진을 축하합니다. 이제 귀하는 Liu 과장이 되셨습니다.
It's so embarrassing. What kind of section chief do you call me?
너무 부끄러워요 나를 어떤 과장이라고 부르나요?
-What should I call you from now on? -Wait me a moment
-이제부터 뭐라고 불러야 하나? -잠시만 기다려주세요
-As you like -Hello?
- 맘대로 - 안녕하세요?
How about calling you the executive?
당신을 임원이라고 부르는 게 어때요?
Oh my god
맙소사
congratulations
축하해요
-Why are you all gathering here? - I will give you more advice in the future.
- 왜 여기 다 모였나요? - 앞으로 더 많은 조언 부탁드리겠습니다.
Okay, got it, thank you
알겠습니다. 감사합니다
-Hi -congratulations
-안녕하세요 -축하해요
Jihyo, why did you come all the way?
지효야, 왜 여기까지 왔니?
congratulations!
축하해요!
Thanks
감사해요
-Please give me some advice -Okay
-조언 좀 해주세요 .
Go back, that's enough
돌아가세요, 그거면 충분해요
Oh, it's true
아, 사실이에요
I'm going crazy
내가 미친거야
Let's go eat something delicious
맛있는거 먹으러 가자
-Okay, no problem . -Really?
- 알았어, 문제없어 - 정말요?
Subtitle translation: Chen Yiying
자막 번역: Chen Yiying